Attack of the Final Boss!
You and I~ Let us go~!
Down to the beach~ Together-
What is that?
Huh?
Aah!
Jun seems to be in high spirits today.
He got a new bike from his parents for his birthday.
And that's not all I got!
Ah, and it looks like Anna gave him that multi-scarf.
I can tell...
Say, what's a birthday?
It's the day he popped out from his mother's belly.
He popped out from a belly?!?!
Not like that...
It's a day to celebrate being born into this world.
Ahh...
So... I guess it's a day to celebrate Jun?
Shouldn't we get something for him too?
You mean... a gift?
But I'm broke.
Hey, what if we save money on fuel...
But fuel prices have gone up!
Hey guys, I have something to discuss with you.
Huh?
This was inside the escape pod we stopped yesterday.
Is it a trailer?
Where's the truck that transports it?
It's likely to be in the part that separated and fell into the sea.
So the owner of this trailer was inside the escape pod?
Jun.
Please look up the data on this trailer using the Metal Breath.
...like this?
Data access complete.
Code name: Heavy Iron.
This belongs to Heavy Iron?!
So he's landed here too, then.
What's wrong? Who is he?
He's one scary Metal Cardbot.
The most powerful and evil outlaw that will use brute force to crush anyone he doesn't like!
He's sure to come here looking for the trailer, since it's a part of his body.
We may already be too late.
Anna!
Too late? What do you mean by that?
Look at this.
Let me see... an oil tanker explodes in the waters near Mowtown.
One survivor said they saw a huge shadowy form swimming in the ocean...
Did it collide with a whale?
No, this is...
Could it be...? Heavy Iron?
For real?!
This is the location where the escape pod landed.
The oil tanker sunk over here.
You mean that... it's headed towards Mowtown?
Let's move the trailer somewhere outside town!
We don't want anyone to get hurt!
Right.
So who's going to tow it?
Hrgh! I knew this was going to happen! UGH!
Stop complaining. I made sure the trailer was properly hitched.
This trailer is super heavy!
Jun! Look!
Listen up.
I want to know where you're planning on taking my other half.
Heavy Iron!
How did he catch up to us so fast?
Huh?
Ha!
There's an empty construction site up ahead!
Let's head over there!
Mega Ambler, Phoenix Fire! Try to keep Heavy Iron busy!
Got it!
Come on then, you outlaw.
Yeah! You'll have to get through us!
Overconfident fools!
This is perfect! We won't attract any attention out here.
What do we do now? Heavy Iron will be here soon.
Let's hide the trailer in that tunnel first!
You'll have to back it in!
Huh? Why should I do that?
If you go in head first, you won't be able to get out.
I'll direct you. Now, hurry up!
Ugh, what a pain.
Heh. Pathetic.
Stop!
He's coming!
Metal Breath, pickup!
Shadow X, setup!
Shadow X, Spinning Cutter!
Spinning Cutter!
Why's he such a hardhead?!
If that's the case, Heli-Tornado!
Got it!
Heli-Tornado!
Haha! How ya like that?!
I don't believe it!
Jun!
Blue Cop, setup!
Blue Cop, Thunderbolt Smash!
Thunderbolt...
Smash!!
Blue Cop! Are you okay?!
Where is my other half?
Right here!
If you want it, then come and get it!
Ha.
Anna, let's take cover!
Now!
-Jun!
-Blue Cop!
Cave in the tunnel's entrance with a Burst Shot!
Got it!
Jun, it worked!
What happened? What'd we miss?
We did it! It's game over for the trailer-truck!
W-what was that?
It couldn't be..?
All of you are nothing but an annoyance.
A bunch of little pests.
All you had to do was hand over my trailer.
Now you're going to pay.
That's... Heavy Iron's true form!
He's much larger than I expected.
And he looks... really angry!
The bigger they are, the harder they fall!
Let's try a rapid fire assault!
Mega Ambler, setup!
Mega Ambler, use Forceps Crush to stop him from moving!
Hngh!
Forceps Crush!
Phoenix Fire, setup!
Your turn, Phoenix Fire!
Burning Hammer!
Yaah! Burning Hammer!
How do you like the heat?!
Hahaha. You couldn't even put a scratch in my iron with that.
I'll show you what true power is!
What is that?
Is he trying to end us all?!
We have to stop him! Hurry up!
Oh! Uh, uhh... Hang on!
Iron Cannon!!
Anna! Are you okay?!
Theo. Are you alright?
I think so... are we still alive...?
Now do you brats understand?
I am the most powerful Metal Cardbot.
I am Heavy Iron!
Now... kneel before me.
Swear loyalty to me, and I will let you live.
You should know well by now that resistance is futile.
W-What the...?
Now's our chance, Blue Cop!
Megabolt Punch!
Megabolt...
Punch!!
I'll let you go today, since I recovered my other half.
However!...
You are going to pay for this!
Thanks, you saved us all.
Hm?
They disappeared.
But... who could that have been?